Guide to the Ithaca House Archive, 1969 - 1986
Ithaca House Archive, 1969 - 1986
- Series I. Author Files
  - Salisbury, Ralph J.,1970-1978 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, reviews, Ithaca House Press Catalogue 10/70-10/72
  - Salisbury, Ralph J.,1970 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Job Query from Education Placement Service - University of Iowa, publicity/jacket blurbs, book sales list for Ghost Grapefruit & Other Poems, table of contents for book, original cover art, printed pages from book, announcements, two poems, two short stories
  - Saltman, Benjamin,1978 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Deck, manuscript
  - Saltman, Benjamin,1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Deck, typescript - final layout version
  - Saltman, Benjamin,1976-1986 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, Library of Congress card, announcements, reviews, reprint permission, announcement & review copy lists
  - Shoemaker, Lynn,1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Coming Home, typescript
  - Shoemaker, Lynn,1978 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Curses and Blessings, typescript
  - Shoemaker, Lynn,1971-1985 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, reviews, announcements, specifications for Coming Home, and Curses and Blessings,, Library of Congress card for Curses and Blessings,, original cover for Curses and Blessings,, 4 poems, miscellany
  - Shrader, Steven,1969 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Leaving by the Closet Door, bound copy, submitted as a thesis for M.F.A. degree, University of Iowa.
  - Shrader, Steven,1970 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Leaving by the Closet Door, in sheets with mock-up.
  - Shrader, Stephen,1970 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Leaving by the Closet Door, in sheets with original cover.
  - Shrader, Stephen,1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, reviews, list of book costs for Leaving by the Closet Door,, news release, IHP catalogue 10/70 - 10/72
  - Silliman, Ron,1971 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Crow, manuscript and book covers
  - Silliman, Ron,1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, copyright requests, reviews, dummy for Crow,
  - Silver-Lillywhite, Eileen,1983 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    All That Autumn, manuscript
  - Silver-Lillywhite, Eileen,1983 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    All That Autumn, final layout version and Library of Congress card
  - Silver-Lillywhite, Eileen,1983 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    All That Autumn, printed version in sheets
  - Silver-Lillywhite, Eileen,1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Mock-ups, reviews, announcements, spec sheet for All That Autumn,, correction notes
  - Silver-Lillywhite, Eileen,1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Correspondence
  - Skillings, Roger,1974 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Alternative Lives, proof
  - Skillings, Roger,1974 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Alternative Lives, manuscript and dummy
  - Skillings, Roger,1974 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Alternative Lives, in sheets with corrections
  - Skillings, Roger,1974 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Alternative Lives, original cover artwork and resume of artist Jane Kogan
  - Skillings, Roger,1974-1980 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    4 short stories, reviews, cost list of Alternative Lives,, address list for review copies of book, announcement
  - Skillings, Roger,1971-1986 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Steinman, Lisa Malinowski,1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Lost Poems, manuscript
  - Steinman, Lisa Malinowski,1975-1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, library of congress card, book cover for Lost Poems,, reviews
  - Swanger, David,1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    The Shape of Waters, manuscript with publisher comments on envelope
  - Swanger, David,1978 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    The Shape of Waters, manuscript
  - Swanger, David,1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Inside the Horse, manuscript
  - Swanger, David,1981 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Inside the Horse, manuscript, dummy, and Library of Congress card
  - Swanger, David,1976-1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, reviews, announcements, cover for The Shape of Waters, Library of Congress card for The Shape of Waters,, photograph of author, photograph for book
  - Tall, Deborah,1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Ninth Life, manuscript
  - Tall, Deborah,1981-1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, reprint permissions, book specifications, reviews, announcements
  - Tharaud, Ross,1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Openings, manuscript
  - Tharaud, Ross,1975-1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, Library of Congress card, reviews, announcements
  - Torgersen, Eric,1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    At War with Friends, manuscript
  - Torgersen, Eric,1971-1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, dummy, 9 poems
  - Walthall, Hugh,1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Ladidah, manuscript
  - Walthall, Hugh,1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Walthall, Hugh,1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Walthall, Hugh,1979 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Spit Curls, manuscript
  - Walthall, Hugh,1977-1982 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Correspondence, book cover, cover photograph
  - Warren, David,1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    World According to Two-Feathers, manuscript
  - Warren, David,1973 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Warren, David,1973 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    World According to Two-Feathers, mock-up
  - Warren, David,1979 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Natural Bone, manuscript
  - Warren, David,1979 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Warren, David,1973-1979 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Material for Natural Bone, and World According to Two-Feathers,, correspondence, reviews
  - Waters, Michael,1974 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Fish Light, manuscript and dummy
  - Waters, Michael,1974 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Fish Light, manuscript
  - Waters, Michael,1974 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Waters, Michael,1974 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Fish Light, sample book
  - Waters, Michael,1974-1985 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Correspondence, reviews, photograph of author, materials for Fish Light,, announcements
  - Wild, Peter,1971 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Peligros, manuscript
  - Wild, Peter,1969-1977 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    Correspondence, material for Peligros,, reviews
  - Woessner, Warren (Box 7, Folder 32)
    correspondence, reviews
  - Unpublished/Rejected Author Files
    - A - Z,1978-1986 (Box 8, Folder 1-55)
- Series II. Business Files
  - Administrative
    - Job Queries,1975 - 1984 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      Arthur - Dunleavy
    - Job Queries,1975 - 1983 (Box 8, Folder 57)
      Durrance - Gilman
    - Job Queries,1977 - 1982 (Box 8, Folder 58)
      Gluck - List
    - Job Queries,1975 - 1982 (Box 8, Folder 59)
      Loeven - Smith
    - Job Queries,1974 - 1979 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      Stearnes - Willsie
    - Letters/info from former employees,1973 - 1984 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Charitable organization registration1980 - 1986 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence,1976 -1977 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Advertising
    - Advertising correspondence and rates,1975 - 1984 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      American Book Review - Library-College Associates
    - Advertising Correspondence and rates,1975 - 1984 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      Library Journal - Threepenny Review
    - IHP Ads,1974 - 1977 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - IHP Ads,1978 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - IHP Ads,1979 - 1984 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Book Related Material
    - Author Address Lists (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Review Copy correspondence,1970 - 1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Review Copy mailing lists,1970 - 1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Reviews of IHP books,1974 - 1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Prize/Award applications and material,1977 - 1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Bookstore/Gallery
    - News Articles about IHP,1970 - 1982 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - IHP Bookstore,1971 - 1978 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      non IHP books sold at IHP, requests from authors to have their books sold at IHP
    - IHP Bookstore/Gallery photos, announcements, hours etc. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Copyright Material
    - Copyright,1971 - 1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      General Information
    - Copyright Registrations,1971 - 1982 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Allardt - Fogel
    - Copyright Registrations,1971 - 1983 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Fortunato - Hathaway
    - Copyright Registrations,1971 - 1982 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      Hewitt - Nathan
    - Copyright Registrations,1970 - 1981 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      Owen - Silliman
    - Copyright Registrations,1972 - 1984 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      Silver-Lillywhite - Woessner
  - Distribution
    - Distribution services info,1975 - 1980 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Serendipity (distributor) and Small press distribution catalogues,1972 - 1978 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Serendipity (distributor) and Small press distribution catalogues,1978 - 1980 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Serendipity (distributor) and Small press distribution catalogues,1981 - 1985 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Serendipity (distributor) and Small press distribution sales reports, receipts, correspondence,1979 - 1984 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Spring Church Book Company Updates/booklists,1983 - 1984 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Financial
    - IHP subscription solicitation letter, subscriptions, book orders, book lists and catalogue,1972 - 1980 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Invoices,1974 - 1981 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      Abt - Arnold
    - Invoices,1970 - 1971 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      Atheneum
    - Invoices,1970 - 1985 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      B and H - Bantam
    - Invoices,1971- 1976 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      Barn Dream Press - Best Cellar Press
    - Invoices,1969 - 1981 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Beyond Baroque - Black Sparrow Press
    - Invoices,1971 - 1985 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      Blackwell North America - Bookslinger
    - Invoices,1971 - 1982 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      Bookstore Press - Burning Deck
    - Invoices,1973 - 1981 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      Callahan Engraving - Copperhead
    - Invoices,1971 - 1976 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      Cornell Campus Store
    - Invoices,1977 - 1979 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Invoices,1970 -1982 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      Cornell University Libraries
    - Invoices,1970 - 1978 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      Cornell University Press - Crazy
    - Invoices,1969 - 1980 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      Da Capo - Dead
    - Invoices,1969 - 1971 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      De Boer
    - Invoices,1972 - 1974 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Invoices,1975 - 1980 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Invoices,1969 - 1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      December - Delacorte Press
    - Invoices,1970 - 1980 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Dick - Dundee
    - Invoices,1970 - 1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Dustbooks - Dutton
    - Invoices,1970 - 1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Earthwords - Eastern News
    - Invoices,1973 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Eastern News
    - Invoices,1974 - 1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Invoices,1970 - 1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Eastern News - Everywoman
    - Invoices,1971 - 1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Falcon - Fiction Collective
    - Invoices,1969 - 1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Fiction Inc. - Fuse
    - Invoices,1969 -1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      G & B - Giligia
    - Invoices,1969 - 1977 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      Giorno - Gunny
    - Invoices,1969 - 1977 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      Halcyone - Harper & Row
    - Invoices,1970 - 1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      Harvard College Library - Hudson Valley
    - Invoices,1970 - 1979 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      IBM - Iowa Review
    - Invoices,1970 - 1979 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      J&A - Kayak
    - Invoices,1971 - 1980 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      KCFR - Kulchur
    - Invoices,1970 - 1979 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      Ladysmith - Lynx
    - Invoices,1971 - 1984 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      Magic Circle - Mc Clane
    - Invoices,1970 - 1980 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      Measure - Mustang Review
    - Invoices,1969 - 1977 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      Naissance - New York Culture Review
    - Invoices,1970 - 1977 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      New York Quarterly - Nova Broadcast
    - Invoices,1969 - 1980 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      Ohio State University Press - Oyez
    - Invoices,1971 - 1979 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      Quality Books Inc. - Portfolio
    - Invoices,1973 - 1977 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      Princeton Paperbacks - Putnam's Sons
    - Invoices,1970 - 1974 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      Random House - Real People Press
    - Invoices,1969 - 1980 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      Red Clay - Russell
    - Invoices,1970 - 1980 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      St. Johnsbury - Sixties
    - Invoices,1969 - 1977 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      Small Farm - Spectrum
    - Invoices,1969 - 1978 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      Spirit that Moves Us - Syracuse New Times
    - Invoices,1970 - 1982 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      Take One - Triangle Book Shop
    - Invoices,1970 - 1981 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      Triaxon Ithaca - Tyndall Creek Press
    - Invoices,1969 - 1980 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      Unicorn Press - Unmuzzled Ox
    - Invoices,1973 - 1977 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      Valley of the Sun - Vintage Books
    - Invoices,1971 - 1980 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      Walden Book Company - Wells College Bookshop
    - Invoices,1970 - 1978 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      Wesleyan University Press
    - Invoices,1969 - 1982 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      West Lithographers - W. W. Norton
    - Invoices,1971 - 1976 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      Yale University Press - Zeitgeist
    - Invoices from Poet's Corner Bookstore,1970 - 1984 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Inventory, operation expenses, sales, etc lists,1969 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Inventory, operation expenses, sales, etc lists,1976 - 1978 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Inventory, operation expenses, sales, etc lists,1979 - 1982 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Inventory, operation expenses, sales, etc lists,1983 -1984 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Grant Material
    - Non NYSCA or UAC Grant Material,1970 - 1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - NYSCA Grant Applications and Material,1978 - 1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - NYSCA Grant Applications and Material,1982 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - NYSCA Grant Applications and Material,1983 - 1984 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Coordinating Council of Literary Magazines Grant Material,1981 - 1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - United Arts Council/Tompkins County Arts Council Grant Material,1980 - 1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - United Arts Council/Tompkins County Arts Council Grant Material,1982 - 1983 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - United Arts Council/Tompkins County Arts Council Grant Material,1983 - 1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - United Arts Council/Tompkins County Arts Council Grant Material,1984 - 1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Catalogs and Announcements
    - Library Mailing Lists (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Catalogue mailing lists (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Announcement mailing lists (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Announcements/Catalogue requests,1975 - 1983 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Library of Congress Material
    - Library of Congress Cataloging In Publication progress reports and article: "The Greatest Invention Since the Title Page?",1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Library of Congress correspondence and Cataloging in Publication info,1974 -1975 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Library of Congress Cataloguing data sheets,1975 - 1985 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Newsletters related to small press and poetry
    - Committee of Small Magazine Editors and Publishers,1969 - 1974 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Committee of Small Magazine Editors and Publishers,1975 - 1982 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Coordinating Council of Literary Magazines,1972 - 1985 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Niagara - Erie Newsletter,1979 - 1980 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Niagara - Erie Newsletter,1981 -1983 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Academy of American poets newsletters, press releases,1981 - 1982 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Academy of American poets newsletters, press releases,1983 - 1984 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Writers and Books Bulletin,1982 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Greenfield Review Newsletter,1982 - 1986 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Writer's Center newsletters and correspondence,1982 - 1984 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Small Press Material
    - NYS Small Press Association Catalogues, sales statements, correspondence,1977 - 1983 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Small Press Racks In Public Libraries (SPRIL) project,1978 - 1979 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - New York State Literary Center small press program,1980 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous
    - 2 Audiocassettes labeled "4 Poets, Fall 78', Syracuse: Marilyn, Lynn, Baxter, Mark",1978 (Box 11)